[dramatic music playing]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[birds chirping]
[imperceptible]
[applauds]
[speaking Japanese]
[woman chuckles]
[baby crying]
[speaking Japanese]
[both chuckle]
[baby continues crying]
[speaks Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
[baby crying]
[squelching]
[water gurgling]
[exhales]
[speaking Japanese]
[baby continues crying]
[mysterious yell]
[man yelling]
[indistinct shouting]
- [gasps]
- [indistinct shouting]
[speaking Japanese]
[indistinct shouting]
[shushing]
[yelling continues]
[woman gasps]
[sword clattering]
[crying quietly]
[exclaims]
- [chuckles]
- [woman gasps]
[icicles crackling]
[crying]
[ominous music playing]
[effort grunt]
[woman screams in distance]
[dramatic music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
[crying]
[speaking Japanese]
[rustling]
[ominous music playing]
[all grunting]
[groans]
[grunting continues]
- [effort grunt]
- [impact grunt]
[indistinct shouting]
[ominous music playing]
[effort grunt]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[shouting]
[ominous music playing]
[whooshes and thwacks]
[slashing]
[intense music playing]
[both grunting]
[groaning]
[icicles crackling]
[groans and breathing heavily]
[both grunting]
[thudding]
[effort grunt]
[both grunting]
[dramatic percussion]
[Hanzo groaning]
[effort grunts]
[speaking Japanese]
[groans]
[baby crying in distance]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[baby crying]
[grunting]
[retches]
[fire crackling]
[rain pattering]
[thunderclap]
[lightning crackling]
[dramatic music playing]
[music crescendos]
[baby cooing]
[lightning crackling]
[dramatic music
continues playing]
[crowd shouting indistinctly]
[Allison] Check it's tight.
Close your hand.
- Feel good?
- Good.
[man] You made it.
Always rely on Cole Young.
Human punching bag.
[exhales]
- Who am I fighting?
- Fighting?
No, no, Cole.
[laughs]
Fighting requires both attacking and
defending, not just throwing punches.
You should try it sometime.
Now don't get sensitive.
You fight Ramirez.
He's, uh... Yeah.
He's experienced, fast,
a good fighter.
Who's your cornerman?
- [chuckling] You're fucking serious?
- You don't like it,
find someone else who'll do this
in an hour's notice for $200.
You're sticking around
for this one?
You know I don't watch him
fight anymore.
Yeah, well. Give the people
a good show, huh?
Or they won't
stick around either.
[all shouting]
[both grunting]
Throw your uppercut!
[crowd cheering and shouting]
[grunting]
Ah!
[crowd cheering and shouting]
[grunting]
Come on!
Don't tap out!
[crowd shouting]
Done! Done!
- [referee] Pack it in.
- [fighter] Yes!
[crowd shouting]
[static]
[dramatic music playing]
[Tsung] The prophecy
is upon us,
which means we could lose
the tenth tournament.
[deep voice] There is
no prophecy.
Hanzo is a ghost.
I killed him centuries ago.
Winning Mortal Kombat
cannot be left to chance.
There will be no tournament
because there'll be
no opposition left to fight.
We will already
be victorious.
Go now and kill Earth Realm's
champions, Bi-Han.
I am no longer Bi-Han.
I am Sub-Zero.
[water splashing]
[sighs]
[ominous music]
[gasps]
Damn, Young.
You're a hell of a fighter, man.
- Thank you.
- Respect.
All right.
- Ready to go?
- In a sec.
What do you got there?
It's a string bracelet.
[sighs]
You just made this?
Yeah.
That's pretty cool.
Want me to put it on?
[groans] My hand.
Now, we got one each.
You're sure you're okay?
Yeah.
Guess I should have thrown
the uppercut, huh?
Cole Young.
The man that took the belt
from Eddie Tobias.
Yeah, that was a long time ago.
Have me met?
No.
Name's Jax.
[Cole] Nice to meet you, Jax.
You could've won today,
had you controlled the cage.
Told you so.
[laughs] She's smart.
All right, well,
time to go eat, yeah.
One more thing, champ.
That dragon logo you got...
I, I dig that, man.
It's unique.
Where'd you get it from?
He was born with it.
- What do you mean?
- It's a birthmark.
You serious?
Pretty cool. Show him.
Well, ain't that something.
Nice chatting with you.
See you around, champ.
- Hey.
- Hi, Mom.
Still in one piece.
How'd it go?
He was this close
to beating him.
- This close.
- Yes.
You sure you're okay?
Standing.
- Let's go order.
- Yeah.
[Jax] Got my eyes
on him right now.
He's got the mark, I saw it.
He's with his family.
Ally.
Come take a look at this.
It's snowing.
[Allison] But it's July.
[crackling]
[dramatic music playing]
- Emily!
- [Allison] Emily!
[car honking]
[tires screeching]
Get in the truck, Cole!
Now!
- [Allison] Come on, come on.
- Move, move, move, move.
[ice crashing]
[tires screeching]
Blade, I got him.
I'll see you at base at 2300.
What the fuck is that thing?
Funny. It didn't sound much
like thanks for saving my ass.
Whatever that was back there,
it's after both of us. Look.
That's, that's impossible.
It's not a birthmark, Cole.
[tires screeching]
- It means you've been chosen.
- Chosen, for what?
- To fight.
- You got the wrong person, all right?
I'm not the fighter
that I used to be, okay.
No, shit.
But they don't have the marking.
So, like it or not Cole,
you're the guy.
As long as you got that marking
they're coming for you,
and they will kill
whoever they have to,
to get to you.
[crackling]
Take the truck.
Get your family to safety.
[Allison] Cole?
[Jax] You need to get
to Gary, Indiana.
Find Sonya Blade,
806 West Washington Boulevard.
Are you sure?
We can take him out together.
[Jax] You want your family on
a fucking slab in the morgue?
Now get out of here.
[gun cocking]
Hold on tight, guys.
[engine revving]
So you wanna play
hide and seek.
[icicles crackling]
[exhales]
[breathing heavily]
[icicles crackling]
[Jax groans]
[grunts]
[Jax grunts]
[groans]
[Jax grunting]
Done six tours, motherfucker.
[Jax grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[screams]
[groans]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[thuds]
She's finally asleep.
[sighs]
I should go.
You'll be safe here, Ally.
You heard what Jax said.
That thing is hunting
people with the marking.
It's after me.
And if I stay here
and it shows up,
it could kill us all.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Jax could have killed it. I...
We have to be sure.
The name he gave me,
Sonya Blade,
hopefully,
she'll have some answers.
[Mileena] Master.
Sub-Zero tracked and killed
another one
of Earth's champions.
But another has escaped.
Have our assassins
double the efforts.
What of Lord Raiden?
If he discovers
we're breaking rules
set in stone
by the Elder Gods...
Leave the Elder Gods to me.
We didn't win
nine straight tournaments
by following the rules.
Mileena, let's finish this.
Send in the reptilian, Syzoth.
[effort grunt]
[dog barks distantly]
[Cole groans]
[both grunting]
- What you doing here?
- Wait.
I'm looking for Sonya Blade.
Jax sent me.
- Where is it?
- Where's what?
The marking.
[breathing heavily]
I'm Sonya.
[Blade] Jax hasn't checked in.
Where is he?
[Cole] He stayed behind
to fight.
Close the door.
Jax, where are you?
[whispers] Come on.
[Cole] You guys in military?
Special forces.
[door creaking]
[Cole] Holy... What is this?
[Blade] We needed a safe place
to run our operation.
[Cole] Well, this looks,
uh, pretty safe.
Looks like you're ready
for anything.
[Blade] This is where we keep
all we've learned
about the dragon markings.
First learned about this
seven years ago.
Jax and I were on a mission
in Brazil
to capture a wanted fugitive.
When we got there,
the target
had superhuman abilities.
Tore through our unit
in seconds.
The target had the same
marking you do, Cole.
When Jax finally took it down
the dragon marking transferred
directly onto his skin.
I spent years trying to
figure out what it all means.
It seems
that throughout history,
different cultures
all over the world,
they reference
a great tournament.
My research shows
that there's realms and species
that we didn't
even know existed.
That dragon marking,
it signifies
that you've been chosen
to fight for Earth.
It's an invitation...
to fight for something known
as Mortal Kombat.
Did you make that last part up?
[chuckles] It just kind
of sounds like you made it up.
I mean, and look,
they spelled it wrong.
Hey, you listen to me.
I think there's another
tournament coming.
That's why you're here.
That is why Jax
and I have been tracking you
because we need to find
every last champion
before it's too late.
And FYI, most of them
are dead already.
There's more to this, Cole.
I know it.
I swear to God, I'm gonna
get to the bottom of it.
- [Kano] I hate to interrupt your bullshit, blondie.
- [gasps]
But I gotta piss again.
What is this?
You have a visitor.
[Blade] Careful, he bites.
Oh, hello, sunshine.
Who are you?
- He's Kano.
- Kano?
Kano, what?
Kano, none of your
fucking business.
Was that Russian?
Do I sound Russian to you,
you fucking idiot?
He's a mercenary
with The Black Dragon clan.
Arms dealer, drug runner,
murder for hire,
scum of the Earth.
I also give
really good foot massages.
You have a marking.
Actually, that's kind of
a funny story.
You want to tell him?
I was tracking
another champion.
I was lucky enough
to find Kano here instead.
Right after he slit
the guy's throat.
You know, next time
be more punctual.
You were never chosen.
Fate has better standards
than you.
Lucky for you
I don't have any standards.
We'll see if you're a natural blonde.
[laughs]
[Kano groans]
[coughs]
Not bad.
Almost felt that one.
[groans]
[Cole] What about you?
- Where's your marking?
- I don't have one.
[crashing]
[Kano] Come on.
Hey, hey, new guy, new guy.
Get me out of here.
I could help you.
Just sit tight.
I was about to go for a stroll,
but maybe I'll stick around,
you fucking idiots.
[lights flickering]
[metal clanking]
[objects clattering]
[creature squeals]
[Kano groans]
- [creature squeals]
- [groans]
[growls]
What the fuck was that?
That was my knife, too!
Fucking poetry.
Where is it?
- Where?
- Shh.
[grunts]
Did you shoot it?
I thought I clipped it.
[Blade groans]
[grunts]
[groans]
Sonya, are you okay?
All right. I'm out of here.
[groans]
[Cole] Kano, use the flare!
[creature squeals]
[Kano] There you are.
[grunts]
[growls]
[all grunting]
[grunting]
Knife.
[both scream]
Kano wins.
[laughs]
You fucking beauty.
[fire blazing]
[Blade] Fucking A,
years of research
just destroyed.
So do you believe me now?
[Cole] Yeah. What's the plan?
[Blade sighs] There is none.
Oh, gee.
Make yourself at home.
Yeah, I have.
Oh, by the way,
you beer's shit,
and you're almost out of it.
[sniffles]
What are you doing?
Just working on
a Kano graphic novel.
I fancy myself
a bit of an artist.
He's a psychopath.
All the best artists
are a little twisted, mate.
[sighs]
Well,
I'm off.
You're trying to get
to Raiden's temple, aren't you?
That should be fun.
You know where that is?
What's Raiden's temple?
Yeah, used to run
guns through there.
The locals
wouldn't shut the fuck up...
[Blade] Legends says champions used
to train there for Mortal Kombat.
Ah, for fuck sake.
No one knows where it is.
Well, they do now.
- Excuse me.
- Where is it?
Uh, you got a pen?
You want to write this down?
Get fucked.
'Cause I'm not gonna help you.
You kidnapped me.
You tied me up.
You threw a knife
through my fucking leg,
on purpose.
And then that lizard thing
took off half my face.
Lucky for me,
you can hardly notice it.
So yeah,
it's a hard pass for me
on the helping you thing.
And get out of me fucking way.
Okay.
[Kano] There you go.
Everyone's got a price.
- Name yours.
- You can't afford me.
Two million.
[laughs]
That's good.
You living in this shit hole
and you got
two million dollars.
Pig's ass.
I have lived here
my whole life.
You piece of shit.
You watch your mouth.
Two million dollars.
Yeah. No, fuck you.
Fuck it. Three million.
That's my final offer.
And anything,
I find inside that temple
I keep, no fucking splitsies.
Plus,
if you're bullshitting me,
I'll fucking kill you.
No skin off my sack.
Great.
- Sounds like we got a deal.
- [clicks tongue]
I was gonna head there anyway.
Yeah, fucking idiot.
[Kano laughs]
How you planning
on getting us there?
Oh, I got a friend
with a plane.
- You got friends?
- Eh, fuck you, pretty boy.
I'm a popular guy.
Everyone loves me.
[snorts]
[spits]
Ooh. [clicks tongue]
Oh, bloody garden gnomes,
they give me the creeps.
You're gonna give that guy
three million dollars?
Fuck, no.
I live in this shit hole.
You think
I got three million dollars?
[dramatic music playing]
[imperceptible]
[gasps]
[Kano] There I was
trying to shove
this guy's nuts
down his throat.
And all I kept thinking about
is what should I get
for me mum for Christmas?
Your mom's been dead
for 30 fucking years, mate.
Kid can dream. Can't he?
Hey, you're out of it.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Thank you for flying Air Kano,
I know you had
fuck all choices.
Afraid time's up.
Time to jump out
of this shit box.
Come on, let's go.
First time?
Yeah. What gave it away?
You'll be okay.
Just gotta jump,
count to three,
pull this side.
All right. Simple. But how...
- Well, do or die, princess.
- [screams]
- What?
- You're fucking kidding me.
So how close are we?
[Kano] Twenty-seven,
twenty-eight K's.
[Blade] What?
Maybe thirty to be safe.
Straight up, thirty-two, eh?
We say thirty-five
there'll be no surprises.
Oh, shit.
Fuck this. I need a break.
- [groans]
- [Cole] You just took a break.
Too many beers, huh?
Give me that GPS.
I'm taking point.
Ah, let's look
at the score board, shall we?
I got us the plane.
I know how to find
your precious little mountain
retreat or whatever it is.
I killed the lizard man.
Huh? Any of you rip
anyone's heart out? Hey.
[laughs] I think I know
what's going on here.
You're jealous, girlie,
of me little marking.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
If you want it so much,
all you got to do is kill me.
Take it.
Now, come on. What do you say?
You want to dance?
- It's your blood.
- Attagirl.
Hmm.
[both grunting]
Go on then, take it.
[panting]
You're so close.
Just take it. Take it!
Nah.
Yeah, that's why
you don't have one of these.
You don't have
the mongrel in you.
[Kano laughs]
You good?
[Kano sighs]
[Kang] At last.
Okay, that's far enough,
MC Hammer.
[screams]
[coughs]
I'm not your enemy.
I'm Liu Kang from
the Shaolin Order of Light.
You're one of
the champions.
Yes, from Earthrealm.
Finally, you have come
to seek out Raiden's...
[stuttering] Fuck the temple.
Wait... You just shot
a fireball out of your hand.
How'd you do that?
Hang on. Hang the fuck on.
Does that mean I'm gonna get
superpowers at any point?
It does, doesn't it?
- There's much to learn.
- The fuck.
But not here.
Follow me.
[Blade scoffs]
[Kano] Hey, David Copperfield.
Hang on.
Just teach me
how you do it.
[dramatic music playing]
There it is...
what you've been
searching for.
It wasn't always
like this.
For thousands of years,
this temple was a holy place
of worship.
It is essential that we begin your
training for the next tournament.
[Cole] This doesn't feel like
a tournament.
So far it feels like an ambush.
[Kang] We don't have much time.
We will not see
another full moon
before the tournament begins.
Come, come. Through here.
[Kano] Now what?
You're gonna make a door appear
out of nowhere?
[rumbling]
[Kano] Oh.
[chuckles]
[Kano] I'll give you that.
It's pretty good.
[Blade] Wow.
[faint crowd screams]
I knew it.
It's all real.
These murals are the living
history of Mortal Kombat.
[scoffs]
[Kano sarcastically] Now
this one really speaks to me.
- [roaring in distance]
- [Blade] This is Outworld.
Yes, the most brutal...
and murderous
of all the realms.
Our greatest enemy.
- [sword slicing]
- [man screaming]
[man speaks indistinctly]
[faint indistinct whispering]
[Kang] We must
start training now.
Before our mortal enemies from
the Outworld come for us.
The fate of Earthrealm
is in our hands.
There are not many of us
with the marking left.
So you must train harder,
and faster.
Because if you fail
to discover your inner power,
you will never defeat
your opponent.
They will ravage everything
you hold dear.
There will be no mercy.
You must fight
without question.
The Dragon has swallowed
many before us.
Now put that back.
Put what back?
[bell chiming]
Jax! Hey, Jax.
[breathing shakily]
Oh, God.
[Kang] It has been
my charge to gather
all the champions of Earth.
By the time I found Jax,
I was too late.
Well, is he gonna live?
The ice...
It cauterized his wounds.
We've sourced every realm
to find a way to heal him.
- What can I do?
- Be patient.
[speaking foreign language]
Give them time
to do their work.
We must go.
He awaits.
[rumbling]
The great protector,
Lord Raiden.
My lord, I've gathered the
remaining champions of Earth.
[Raiden] This is what
I have to work with?
You are in no physical
or mental shape to fight.
You don't even have a marking.
[Kano] All right, hang on.
What about me, Gandalf,
where's my fortune cookie jar...
[lightning crackling]
- Powerless, arrogant.
- [groans]
The time has long passed.
Our enemies have claimed
nine straight victories.
One more victory and Outworld will
gain control over Earth forever,
and Shang Tsung will enslave
the entire human race.
[coughs]
Sorry, what did I miss?
[Cole] They tried
to kill my family.
Help us.
There's nothing for you here,
only death.
Well, I'm willing to die
for my family.
[Raiden] Let's see if you have
what it takes.
[whooshes]
[rumbling]
[grunts]
[Kang groaning]
[crunching]
- [slicing]
- [yelping]
[swooshing]
[panting]
[speaking foreign language]
The time has come
to end this.
Take whatever trophies
you desire...
- but their souls are mine.
- [Raiden] Silence!
[lightning crackling]
I've come to claim your world.
You're too late, Raiden.
It is forbidden to claim victory
until the tournament begins.
You are correct, Thunder God.
The conflict outside of Mortal
Kombat is not forbidden.
- [munching] -Besides the other
guards are too lazy to stop me.
I have come for your souls.
You will leave this place
at once, sorcerer.
These are your champions?
Kill them.
[blades swishing]
- [Raiden grunts]
- [thudding]
[roaring]
[lightning crackling]
You think these tricks
will protect you forever?
Only a matter of time.
[electrical buzzing]
[metallic thud]
[mumbles] This totally make up
my superpowers.
Think I get it now.
It's kind of like a box of chocolates.
You never know what you're gonna get.
Is it gonna be fireballs?
Is it gonna be
lightning, huh?
Could be shit. Could be, uh...
Could be a frisbee hat.
No offense, whoever you are.
The name is Kung Lao.
Descendant of
the Great Kung Lao.
[Lao] The grand champion
of the Order of Light.
Never heard of him.
[Kang] Listen carefully.
Your training has begun.
Come.
[electrical buzzing]
[Kang] Your inner power
comes from your arcana,
a gift from the marking
of the Dragon.
The point of your training is
for you to unlock that power.
Without it, defeating Outworld
will be impossible.
Kung Lao and I have discovered
our arcana.
In the fight pit,
you'll discover yours.
You may enter.
[Kano chuckling]
Let's do the damn thing.
[applauds]
I want your fireballs.
- There is no guarantee...
- So, Liu, instead of fireballs,
what else is gonna shoot out of my hands?
Like, knives or guns...
Hey, do you
ever shut up?
You're welcome to
stay with us, Miss Blade.
But the training area
is for the chosen ones only.
[scoffing] Fucking whoops.
Well, hang on.
We wouldn't be here
without her.
She's one of us.
A fighter without a marking
can never achieve their arcana.
And a fighter without an arcana
is a liability to the others.
Yeah, liability.
All right. Bye, bye, blondie.
All right, guys.
Little less of this.
Little more of this.
Come on.
[Lao] Be still and listen.
[whispering] Fuckin' hell.
[gasping]
[Blade] Jax.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
I'm here.
Hi, buddy.
[breathing heavily]
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
You just lay down.
What happened?
[Kang] All you can do now
is test your might.
We have no time to lose.
You must unlock your arcana.
[both grunting]
[swishing]
[metallic clang]
[Cole yelping]
[impact grunt]
[Cole groaning]
[Lao] In Mortal Kombat,
talent will only get you so far.
[Kano applauding]
[mockingly]
No, that was great. Really.
Good stuff.
You know, maybe your arcana is
getting your ass kicked by a hat.
[chuckles]
[inhales]
[exhales]
Fight!
No Harry Potter shit,
all right?
[yelps and groans]
[Kano] Cute.
Real cute.
[laughs] Let's see.
Throwing down again?
[grunting]
Is that the only move
you know, mate?
- [Kang grunts]
- [screams] Fuck.
[groans]
Yeah, yeah.
Put a fucking shirt on, Magic Mike.
It seems as though we have
our work cut out for us.
[Kano] I was just warming up.
[Kang] Let me see your wound.
[Cole groaning]
Liu...
How do I find my arcana?
It must come
from your soul.
Whatever it is that drives you.
So how did you find
your arcana?
Unlike Kung Lao,
I was just a worthless stray.
For reasons beyond my ken,
Master Bo' Rai Cho found me
half dead in the gutter
- and brought me to the Wu Shi Academy.
- [groans]
There, I was given a purpose.
A brother...
Kung Lao.
And I met Lord Raiden.
Kung Lao and I
have served together.
Upon graduation,
I was given a name of a man.
He was a purveyor
of rare things.
Children.
Orphans like me.
He had a marking,
so I chose to
take it from him.
And in that moment,
my arcana came forth.
- [fire blazing]
- [groans]
[men grunting]
[swishing]
[coughing]
[smacking]
[Blade] Come on, Major.
I've seen better than that.
Again. Again. Again!
- [effort grunt]
- Come on, you got this.
[grunting]
These don't work.
These are not me.
I'm useless.
Why even bring me here?
I can't help.
My first day of training...
We had to run 20 miles.
[chuckles]
Thought I was gonna die.
I wanted to quit,
but all I ever wanted
was to be accepted by you...
as an elite fighter.
You remember what you told me?
How do we keep going?
And you proved to yourself
that you can do this or...
regret it for the rest
of your life.
Are you trying to tell me
something, soldier?
Get off your fucking ass,
Major.
[laughs]
Miss Sonya, sit, please.
- Ah, thank you.
- [Kang] Eat.
Cole, how's your arm?
[groans] It's healing up.
[Kang] Eat more, heal fast.
More training tomorrow.
You're fucking
kidding me, aren't you?
[laughing] Fucking hell.
Is he on our side?
[sarcastically]
Those are great, mate.
They make those
in men's sizes?
[laughing]
[snaps fingers]
Top knot, at the end.
What's his name?
Kung Pao.
Pass us some fucking egg roll,
would you?
[speaking foreign language]
Your ear is painted on, mate?
Egg roll.
There you go.
Good boy.
- [chuckling]
- [Blade chuckling]
Maybe you should lay off
the egg rolls,
seeing how you wouldn't be
ready to fight
if you had 100 days to train.
[Lao] I'll dumb it down
for you.
Fat, lazy pig.
What did you say?
Terrible fighter.
Zero skill.
You got a death wish, mate?
Combat takes intelligence.
But you...
You're like a dog.
A dog who fails
his training classes.
Well, how about I take that stupid
fucking sombrero you're wearing,
shove it so far up your ass,
you start speaking Spanish.
How does that sound?
You can try.
I just fucking might.
Let me ask you this.
Why would you
jeopardize the goodwill
of the only chance
of your survival?
Princess, why don't you try
being one of them silent monks?
No, no, you misunderstand.
He is here to save you
because you cannot
save yourself.
- Oh, fuck, here we go.
- You're like...
an aggressive little bunny.
- Soft and useless.
- [all chuckling]
Angry mentally, physically.
You should be on your knees
before this man.
[Blade and Jax chuckling]
I've a better idea.
How about you two
get on your knees
and take turns
sucking my sack?
[chopsticks clang]
Do you have any fucking
idea who you're talking to?
I'm wanted in over
35 countries for shit,
you fucking ballerinas
couldn't even imagine.
- [thuds]
- You're angry.
Oh! Fucking nothing
gets by you, does it?
Good.
You should be.
You failure.
[softly] Failure?
Fucking failure?
Let me educate you,
motherfucker. I'm Kano.
I'm the black fucking dragon.
And who are you two, huh?
You're some fucking
cave-dwelling hippy,
twirling his anal beads,
taking orders
from this Wu Shu wanker,
who wears
a hubcap as a helmet.
Now, sit down!
Shut up and pass me
a fucking egg roll.
[buzzing]
[objects clattering]
[breathing heavily]
That was it, wasn't it?
You all saw that? [laughing]
[excitedly]
Laser beam!
It's better than fireballs,
you pussy.
[laughing hysterically]
Come on, Kano.
I knew I'd get mine first.
[laughing]
[exhales]
[electrical buzzing]
[Kang] We are running
out of time, Cole.
Focus on what you can't deny.
Find the truth in you.
The pain.
It's the ultimate catalyst.
[groans]
- Again.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa... Hold on.
Does it have to be him? I...
[both grunting]
You know, I see a little bit
of arcana there.
Give me one more crack at it.
[Kang] Focus on the pain, Cole.
- I'm focusing, nothing's happening. It hurts...
- [Kano] Stick with it.
Again.
[groans]
Yeah, you're right.
Nothing's happening.
You're as lazy, ya?
[panting]
[electrical buzzing]
[exhales]
What are you looking at?
They're beautiful.
You're a lucky man.
Thanks.
You have failed
to find your arcana.
Without it, you are a liability
to the others.
So where did this come from?
And why am I the only champion that
had the marking since I was born?
Your marking comes
from your lineage, Cole.
Lineage?
I'm an orphan
from the south side of Chicago.
You're a descendant of one of the
greatest ninjas to ever walk the Earth.
Hanzo Hasashi.
[sword swishing]
He was murdered along
with his wife and eldest son
by the same assassin
that hunts you now.
Sub-Zero.
[Raiden] The moment he died,
Hanzo descended into the Netherrealm,
the furthest reaches of hell,
endlessly searching
for revenge.
But his bloodline lived on.
I rescued Hanzo's
only surviving child...
and hid her in the one place
he wouldn't think to find her.
For centuries,
the Hasashi marking
has passed down
through your ancestors.
I had a hope the power in your
bloodline was still strong in you.
Now I know that's not the case.
[lightning crackling]
[lightning buzzing]
Go, be with your family.
Cole, do not give up on this.
I'm sorry.
[thunder rumbling]
[Nitara screeching]
[Tsung] Welcome.
The great hunter, Nitara.
She is beautiful, isn't she?
Yeah. That screech
is a real turn on.
My loyal warriors, Kabal,
General Reiko,
I have seen the so-called
champions of Earth realm,
and they're no match
for all of you.
We are on
the precipice of victory
and taking Earth realm forever.
But we must strike now.
Raiden has prevented entry
into his temple.
I must find a way
to bring his shield down
in order to obliterate
our opposition.
I think I can help.
Did you see a guy down there?
A complete fucking asshole.
Answers to Kano.
- Kano.
- Yeah.
He's the reason I live
in an iron lung.
He's a low life,
piece of shit scumbag.
You're going to love him.
[gate opening]
Prince Goro.
It is an honor to have
Shokan blood on our side.
Now we shall end this prophecy
once and for all.
Well, well, well.
You backstabbing, two-faced
ugly motherfucker.
- Kabal.
- Hey, Kano.
It's been a while.
You getting enough sleep, mate?
Your eyes are a little
redder than usual.
You've got a big mouth
for someone who's standing
on the wrong side of
the electric fence, tough guy.
You working
for the other fella?
- That wizard?
- Working with him, not for him.
And trust me, it has its perks.
Like what?
This is fucking tragic.
Look at yourself.
You used to be someone to fear.
You've fallen down a long way
since you led the Black Dragon.
Don't tell me about
the Black Dragon.
I am the Black Dragon.
Which one's your boss?
Let me guess. The blonde?
That mask cutting off your
air supply, you dumb prick?
I don't take orders
from anyone, Kabal.
Then you're on the wrong side.
Fight with us and you could
have more money
than you know what to do with.
Hell, you could turn this
old temple into your own casino
if you wanted to.
Just name your price,
then double it and double it again.
What are you
waiting for, asshole?
[clears throat] So what would
I need to do?
[thuds]
Just wait here.
[grunts]
[laughs maliciously]
[ominous music playing]
What is that?
[Kano] You know, the problem
with these new lightning sticks,
they just don't make them
like they used to.
[chuckles]
What? You didn't think you'd
actually change me, did you?
The undoing of the prophecy
has begun.
[grunts]
Back inside.
Dad!
Get back inside!
[grunts]
[Allison] Cole!
Hey!
I'm the one you want.
You see that!
Okay.
[grunts]
Finish them!
[grunting]
[growls]
- [growls]
- [groans]
[both grunting]
Damn! Your breath stinks.
[grunts]
[impact grunt]
[screams]
[grunting]
[grunts and screams]
[breathing heavily]
This is not the blood
of the Chosen One.
Your death has no worth.
[Kano] Ah, girls can be mean!
- Don't worry, darling!
- [grunts]
You're still good enough
for me.
[grunts in pain]
[chuckles]
[grunting]
Want me to slow down a little?
[Tsung] You're beneath me.
Now, destroy him, my beauty.
[Nitara screeches]
[muffled screeching]
[effort grunt]
[both grunting]
[yells]
Flawless victory.
[gasps]
- No!
Now I tear out your spine,
champion!
Fuck this.
[both grunting]
- [coughs]
- Mom!
[chokes]
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
- [Allison] Come on! Come on! Come on!
- [engine revs]
[Allison and Emily scream]
[Allison] No, no.
Mom!
[Allison] Get closer!
[grunts]
No, Mom!
Aah!
[Allison] Cole!
Allison!
[impact grunt]
Aah!
[effort grunt]
Get off me!
[growls and grunts]
[growls]
Daddy, use your uppercut!
[grunts]
[coughs]
[both grunting]
[screams]
[grunts]
[Cole breathing heavily]
[Cole and Allison sigh]
You okay?
We're fine. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Badass suit, Dad.
[sighs wearily]
Blade!
[effort grunt]
Help!
[breathing heavily]
[effort grunt]
[lightning crackling]
- What's that?
- It's okay.
It's a doorway back...
It's not over.
Impossible.
Thank you for helping
my fighter find his arcana.
After 4000 years, the Hasashi
bloodline still lives on.
Bi-Han.
[lightning crackling]
Stop him!
[impact grunt]
Your soul's mine.
[Lao screaming]
He's about
to get his soul sucked.
I love the scream
right before...
[both grunting]
[Lao screaming]
- Gotcha.
- [gasps]
[screaming]
[screams]
Shang Tsung!
No!
[Blade] Where are we?
[Raiden] We are in the void.
It is the realm
between your world and mine.
Shang Tsung
cannot follow us here.
If we're to die...
it was supposed
to be together.
I'm sorry, Liu Kang.
Without Kung Lao,
Earthrealm is lost.
[Jax] Lord Raiden.
Why couldn't you save him?
All the Gods are forbidden
from engaging in one realm's
war against another.
It is my job
to protect Earthrealm
but I cannot save
every soul within it.
No.
It's not over,
we still need to fight.
Cole.
The blood on this blade
is your ancestors.
Hanzo Hasashi's.
I took it from him
the day he died.
Use it and the spirit of Hanzo
fights with you.
So what's the plan?
We need to fight smarter.
We need to control the fight.
How?
I mean, they're better trained
and better prepared.
Plus they don't mind
breaking the rules.
We need to split them up.
Lord Raiden,
can you send anyone anywhere?
Well, they don't want
a tournament.
Let's give them one.
But let's do it our way.
Give me Reiko.
I got a score to settle.
Hey, big boy!
[screams]
Sonya...
Please tell me I get
the bitch with the teeth.
You get to take out
your old buddy, Kano.
I know I've seen you
kick his ass before,
but he's got a laser now.
Watch out for that.
Oh, I got an idea.
Honey, I'm home.
You and I will take
Mileena and Kabal.
I know this is
personal for you.
Are you ready?
[Kabal] You again.
What about Sub-Zero?
Nobody's taking him
out one on one.
Yeah.
We save Sub-Zero for last.
We take him out together
as a team.
[grunts]
[grunting]
Oh-oh.
[screams]
[both grunting]
[groaning]
[effort grunt]
Yeah, these motherfuckers work.
[screams]
Ah! Damn it!
I'd come out if I were you.
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[groaning]
Oh!
Fucking bitch!
[screams]
Hey!
[screams and grunts]
[both grunting]
And you owe me...
three million dollars.
[both grunting]
Fucking hell!
This is a bit harder
than I thought.
- [Blade grunts]
- [chuckles]
Tell me, blondie,
how does that feel?
[gasps]
It was fucking amazing...
- Oh!
- ...mate.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[chuckles]
[grunting]
[gasps]
Oh, I'm sorry, did I cut ya?
[screams]
What the fuck!
[grunts]
[dragon screeching]
[Kabal screams]
[Kang speaking
foreign language]
For Kung Lao.
[screams]
Shit!
A little help!
[grunting]
That's pretty cool.
Little parting gift from Kano.
[Allison] Okay.
I'm almost ready.
How about you?
Are you sure Dad's gonna be
able to find us?
Completely sure.
Look, I just want to get us out of here.
Fuck another four armed monster
showing up.
[ominous music playing]
[portal whooshes]
[Cole] Emily!
No! Emily! No!
Allison... [grunts]
Finally the Hasashi bloodline
will end.
[screams]
[grunting]
[impact grunt]
Now you will die
with your family.
[grunts]
[screams]
The blade of Hanzo.
[grunts]
[music crescendos]
Get over here.
[Sub-Zero grunts]
[speaking foreign language]
[both grunting]
[groans]
[blade whistles]
[speaking foreign language]
[icicles crackling]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[groans]
[Cole screaming]
[grunts]
[speaking foreign language]
[all grunting]
[impact grunt]
[coughs]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[groans]
[groaning]
[both grunting]
[both gasp]
[panting]
[effort grunt]
For the Lin Kuei.
[all grunting]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
[speaking foreign language]
[icicles crackling]
- Dad.
- [softly] Okay. I got you.
[speaking foreign language]
[Sub-Zero screams]
[dramatic music playing]
[speaking foreign language]
[fire crackling]
[lightning crackling]
These are my friends.
I am Liu Kang.
Sit. I will warm you.
I'm impressed.
I thought you said
you couldn't get involved.
[ominous music playing]
Shang Tsung.
[Raiden] The prophecy
has been fulfilled.
Has the blood on your hands
taught you nothing?
[Tsung] No matter how many of
my people you put in the ground,
there will always be another
to take their place.
Today you have killed
my warriors
and you think you have won.
But death
is only another portal.
[whooshes]
Next time I see you,
I will not bring fighters.
I will bring armies.
You will return to Outworld
at once.
Earthrealm...
[lightning crackling]
He talks so much.
[Cole] What happens next?
Today we are victorious.
But there are other enemies
to fight.
We cannot let our guard down.
I'll assemble a new list
of champions.
You must find them.
Who's first?
My man,
I was just about to call you.
I need you tomorrow night.
Sorry. My days fighting
for 200 bucks are done.
Oh, you're finally quitting,
huh?
Yeah, uh, something like that.
Where're you gonna go?
Hollywood.
Hollywood? What the hell's
in Hollywood?
Not what, who.
It's been fun.
[scoffs]
Hollywood. [scoffs]
[upbeat music playing]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[music continues playing]